[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the three sacred stones Indiana Jones is searching for in the movie Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom?", "correct_answer": "Shankara Stones", "incorrect_answers": ["The Pankot Stones", "Sri Lanka Stones", "The Temple of Caliph Stones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous line Ill be back, or a variation of it, was used in which Terminator movie?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Terminator Salvation", "Terminator 2: Judgment Day", "The Terminator"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nicknamed Mighty Mo (or Big Mo), this Iowa-class battleship from the end of World War II was the last battleship built by the United States.", "correct_answer": "USS Missouri", "incorrect_answers": ["USS Illinois", "USS Idaho", "USS Minnesota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means fear of prostitutes or venereal disease?", "correct_answer": "Cypridophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Cynophobia", "Cyclophobia", "Cymophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Woody Allen movie Vicky Cristina Barcelona, Scarlett Johanssons character is in Barcelona to complete her masters in Catalan identity.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take for the planet Earth to orbit the Sun once?", "correct_answer": "365 Days", "incorrect_answers": ["2 Years", "8 Months", "24 Hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why would Romans and Egyptians eat some lettuce leaves after dinner?", "correct_answer": "To stimulate sleep", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "To improve the braking down of fats", "To improve digestion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the cause of strawberry allergic reactions, such as the Oral allergy syndrome?", "correct_answer": "The red pigment in the fruit", "incorrect_answers": ["The presence of a toxin in the fruit", "Citric acid", "The seeds of the fruit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many children does Mel Brooks have from his two marriages?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "6", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song from the movie Camp Rock was performed by the Jonas Brothers?", "correct_answer": "Play My Music", "incorrect_answers": ["We Rock", "Gotta Find You", "This Is Me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter is the fourth brightest object in the sky.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the science fiction movie Soylent Green released?", "correct_answer": "1973", "incorrect_answers": ["1975", "1977", "1974"]}]